The alpha discovery phase is where the fun really starts.
alpha 挖掘阶段非常有趣
This is when you start looking for alphas,
这个阶段你需要寻找潜在 alpha
but what are alphas exactly?
到底什么是 alpha？
An alpha is an expression applied to
alpha 是个表达式
the cross-section over your universe of stocks which returns
应用在股票池里的股票切面数据上
a vector of real numbers whose values are
该表达式会返回一个实数向量
proportional to the size of the position you will take on each asset.
向量值与你对每个资产的持仓大小成比例
You can think of the numerical output of an alpha as providing an indication,
可以将 alpha 的数值输出看做一种
or metric of conviction about
表示未来收益率的指标
future returns which will ultimately inform a trading decision.
你将根据该指标做出最终交易决策
When you have discovered a successful alpha,
当你发现成功的 alpha 后
the value in that vector for each stock is directly proportional
向量中每支股票的值
to the rank of its return at a future time across the universe of stocks.
与股票在备选投资组合中的未来收益排名直接成比例
For example, in a cross-sectional momentum strategy,
例如 在横截面动量策略中
we rank the stocks according to how much momentum
我们根据股票所具有的动量（由动量指标衡量）
they have as measured by a momentum indicator.
对股票进行排序
We use the ranks to decide which stocks to put in along
我们根据排名决定在每个时间点上
portfolio and which stocks to put in a short portfolio at every time interval.
将哪些股票放入做多投资组合中 将哪些股票放入做空投资组合中
In this scenario, you can think of the logic that produces the ranks as the alpha,
在这种情形下 你可以将生成排名的逻辑看做 alpha
and the ranks themselves as the alpha vector.
将排名本身看做 alpha 向量
Taken together, the ranks are a vector of numbers that help
排名是一个数字向量
inform the trading decision of which docs to hold long and short,
有助于我们做出交易决策 例如做多和做空哪些股票
and in what amounts.
投资多少金额
An alpha is one type of trading signal.
alpha 是一种交易信号
A trading signal is a general term for
交易信号是一个很宽泛的术语
any numerical signal that can be used to inform a trade.
表示可以用来做出交易决策的任何数字信号
It could just be a single number.
它可以是单个数字
Therefore, alphas which are vectors are a subset of trading signals.
所以作为向量的 alpha 也属于交易信号
The alpha discovery phase can also be called the signal research phase.
发现 alpha 阶段也称为信号研究阶段
This stage is where you test your hypothesis and see if you can come up with
在此阶段 你将检验你的假设
evidence that your idea may lead to strong future returns.
并看看是否有证据证明你的想法能带来可观的未来收益
This will be an iterative process.
这将是一个迭代过程
However, in modern markets,
但是 在现代市场中
it's rare that a single alpha will provide
单个 alpha 很少能提供
sufficiently consistent positive returns
足够一致的正收益率
to provide the sole basis of an investment strategy.
并成为投资策略的唯一依据
Typically, several alphas will be combined together to generate
通常 需要将多个 alpha 组合到一起
an overall alpha that has better performance than the best individual alpha.
生成一个比单个 alpha 业绩更好的总体 alpha
This is akin to the ideas of model
这就相当于
stacking and ensembling in traditional machine learning.
传统机器学习中的模型堆叠和组合
Combining alphas that have diverse inputs and
将输入和底层假设各不相同的 alpha 组合到一起
underlying hypotheses can lead to a high-quality combined alpha vector.
可以形成高质量的组合 alpha 向量
For example, a price-driven alpha such as the momentum alpha may
例如 基于价格的 alpha（例如动量 alpha）
combined well with an alpha based on
与基于公司基本面的 alpha 相组合可能会效果不错
company fundamentals since the inputs are very different.
因为输入很不相同
In this phase, alphas may be combined using simple logic like adding ranks are averaging,
在此阶段 可以使用简单逻辑组合 alpha 例如将排名相加或取平均值
or through more complicated waiting schemes like finding
或通过更复杂的加权方法进行组合
the weights that lead to the lowest possible variance for the combined alpha.
例如寻找使组合 alpha 的方差尽可能小的权重
Another possible method is to translate your alphas into features and use them as
另一种方法是将 alpha 变成特征
inputs to a machine learning classifier to capture the relationships between the alphas.
并将它们输入到机器学习分类器中 从而发现 alpha 之间的关系
The output of this stage is a single alpha vector that
这个阶段的输出是一个 alpha 向量
incorporates the information of many individual alphas.
其中包含了很多 alpha 的信息